meeton.com 2017-03-30

# MeetON.com

### PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy applies to MeetON.com. Live Enterprise, LLC d/b/a MeetON.com ("MeetON.com", "we", "us", or "our") provides content streaming and social networking capabilities that enable the sharing of live and recorded video and audio content and chat via the Internet, mobile, and other data delivery means through MeetON.com’s proprietary platform (the "Service") and our website accessible at meeton.com (the "Site").

We are providing this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of the Site. Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy are defined in the MeetON.com [Terms of Service](http://www.meeton.com/terms-legal.html), which are incorporated herein by reference.

As used in this policy, the terms "using" and "processing" information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within the United States or internationally.

**We work closely with Market America Worldwide, Inc. and its subsidiaries, Market America, Inc., Shop MA, Inc. dba SHOP.COM, and SHOP.COM Marketplace, Inc. ("Our Affiliates") and your personal, technical, and discretionary information may be shared with each of these Affiliates, in our discretion. For this reason, throughout this Privacy Policy, references made to "MeetON.com", "we", "us", or "our" also include Our Affiliates.**

By using or accessing MeetON.com or the Service, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

  * **Information Collection and Use**

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve the Service, features and content, to administer your membership, and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site. We also may also use your information in order to better understand how the Service is used. It is not our practice to sell, rent, or trade personal information.

    * In the course of using the Service, we ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you and administer your account ("Personal Information"). Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, credit card or other billing information, email address, home and business postal addresses, and Site usage information. We use your Personal Information mainly to provide the Service and administer your inquiries. 
    * Please be aware that when you register on our Site, other users of the Service may be able to see your screen or user name, in addition to any comments or submissions that you post to the Site or submit via the Service. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information and that you not use your real name as your screen or user name to the extent that allows others to identify you. Your Personal Information may be shared with law enforcement and other third parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy and subject to all applicable laws. 
    * We also collect the other information that you provide as part of your use of the Service, including via your registration and the administration and personalization of your profile webpage (e.g., without limitation zip code, gender, age and individual preferences) ("Non-Identifying Information"). Certain Non-Identifying Information would be considered a part of your Personal Information if it were combined with other identifiers (for example, combining your zip code with your street address) in a way that enables you to be identified, but the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other non-identifying information (for example, your viewing preferences). We may combine your Personal Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other users of the Service to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the Service and to analyze and understand how the Service is used. 
    * We also use your Personal Information to contact you with marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. 
    * We may also share and use your Personal Information with other networks, websites and entities affiliated, owned, controlled and/or connected with MeetON.com. We will use your Personal Information in compliance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. 
    * We may offer special access to pay-per-view or other special promotional events (e.g., live broadcast of concerts), and we may share your Personal Information, excluding including banking or credit card information, with those entities, broadcasters, and advertisers that are participating in such event. 
    * We may share your Personal Information with law enforcement, governmental agencies, or authorized third-parties, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity or any other activity that may expose us, you, or any other broadcaster or user to legal liability. In such events, we will disclose information relevant to the investigation, such as name, city, state, ZIP code, telephone number, email address, user history, IP address, and anything else we may deem relevant to the investigation. 
    * If you make a charitable donation on MeetON.com, we may send the charitable organization some or all of the following personal information so that the organization can send you a receipt: your name, mailing address, and email address. 
    * If you are a Broadcaster, we may ask for your tax identification number and bank account information, which we will use to pay you for your share of revenues for broadcasts containing your Broadcaster Content. 
    * If MeetON.com sells all or part of this Site or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, we may, in our sole discretion, transfer, sell or assign your Personal Information to a third party as part or in connection with that transaction. Upon such transfer, the Privacy Policy of the acquiring entity may govern the use of your Personal Information. 
    * Information posted to message boards, chat rooms, blogs and other user forums become public information. Use caution when posting. Individuals under the age of 18 should use additional care not to provide any personally identifying information when participating in any area of the Site where postings might become public. We are not responsible for Personal Information you submit in connection with these areas on the Site, nor are we responsible for how others might use that information, including to send you unsolicited messages. 
    * California Law permits users who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [privacy@meeton.com](mailto:privacy@meeton.com). 
  * **Coookies, IP Addresses, and Other Software and Hardware Attributes**

As you interact with the Site, we collect certain Site use information. This information is collected for all users. When you enter the Site, we collect your IP address, browser type, and other software and hardware attributes. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using cookies. A cookie is a small data file that is stored by your web browser on your computer. The cookies we use include, without limitation, session ID cookies and persistent cookies. This data may be used for security purposes, to track usage and to manage and improve the Site. Cookies also allow us to enhance, personalize and track your online experience, so that the information you receive is more relevant to you. This technology will allow you to move faster through our Site once the information is in our database since you do not have to re-enter the same information each time you enter the Site. Session ID cookies confirm that you are logged in. These cookies terminate once you close your browser. Persistent cookies store your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to the Site. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent; however, it is possible that some parts of the Service will not function properly if you do.

  * **Legal Considerations**

On rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a subpoena or court order, or when required by law to do so. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to report and/or prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the Site, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.

  * **Third Party Advertising**

Advertisements that appear on the Site are sometimes delivered directly to users by third party advertisers. The third party advertiser will automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. MeetON.com does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on the Site unless you choose to share it with them. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by MeetON.com on the Site and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

Additionally, these third party advertisers may serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit the Site. These companies may use Non-Identifying Information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this Site and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org.

  * **Changing or Deleting Your Information**

At any time, you may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in your registration profile by contacting us. If you completely delete all such information, then your account may become deactivated. If you would like us to delete your record in our system, please contact us and we will attempt to accommodate your request. See below for privacy contact information.

  * **Security**

We employ reasonable physical, technological, and administrative security measures and attempt to ensure they are applicable under the circumstances. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored Personal Data (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

  * **Our Policy Toward Children**

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 14. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [privacy@meeton.com](mailto:privacy@meeton.com). If we become aware that a child under the age of 14 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

  * **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@meeton.com](mailto:privacy@meeton.com) or at:

Legal Department  
Live Enterprise, LLC d/b/a MeetON.com  
3250 NE 1st Ave., Suite 305  
Miami, Florida 33137
  * **Policy Changes**

From time to time, we may use your information for unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change, we will post these changes in the Site. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy periodically.

  * **Your Consent**

By using the Site or by continuing to use the Service, you consent to the collection and use of your information as detailed in this Privacy Policy.

  * **Privacy Policy, Terms of Service, Notices and Revisions**

This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms of Service, all policies currently posted on the Site, all policies that may be posted by us on the Site in the future, and any additional terms to which you agree in order to use certain parts of the Site, shall constitute the entire agreement between you and MeetON.com concerning the Service. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time. All changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, upon their posting on this Site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate on the applicable policy or agreement the new effective date. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current Privacy Policy.

Updated: January 20, 2013
